const questions = [
	{question: "Which of the following materials is not commonly recyclable?",
	choices: ["Glass", "Paper", "Plastic bags", "Aluminum cans"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What does the recycling symbol with three arrows represent?",
	choices: ["Reduce, Reuse, Recycle", "Recycle, Replace, Renew","Reuse, Recycle, Restore", "Reduce, Renew, Reclaim"],
	correctAnswer: 0},

	{question: "What is e-waste?",
	choices: ["Waste from agricultural practices", "Waste from electronic devices", "Waste from chemical spills", "Waste from construction sites"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "How can you reduce the amount of carbon emissions?", 
	choices: ["Plant a tree", "Carpool", "Keep the lights on when you leave the house", "Both a and b"],
	correctAnswer: 3},

	{question: "What is composting?",
	choices: ["Burning waste to reduce volume", "Burying waste in landfills", "Recycling organic waste into fertilizer", "Disposing of waste in oceans"],
	correctAnswer: 2}, 

	
	{question: "Which ecosystem will not be affected by climate change?",
	choices: ["Rainforest", "Ice caps", "Desert", "None of the above"],
	correctAnswer: 3},

	{question: "Why is deforestation bad?",
	choices: ["Less trees to absorb carbon dioxide", "Increases soil erosion", "Decreases biodiversity", "All of the above"],
	correctAnswer: 3},

	{question: "Which of the following actions can help reduce plastic pollution?",
	choices: ["Using disposable coffee cups", "Using reusable shopping bags", "Using single-use water bottles", "Using plastic straws"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "Which material is known to be infinitely recyclable without degrading in quality?", 
	choices: ["Glass", "Paper", "Plastic", "Cardboard"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "Which of the following is not a fossil fuel?",
	choices: ["Oil", "Coal", "Biofuels", "Natural gas"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	
	{question: "Which type of energy uses the heat from Earth’s interior?",
	choices: ["Nuclear", "Geothermal", "Kinetic", "Potential"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "What percentage of Earth’s water is freshwater?",
	choices: ["70%", "3%", "1%", "25%"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What is a carbon sink?",
	choices: ["Something that sequesters carbon", "When carbon sinks when you put it in water", "A kitchen sink made of carbon", "Sustainable construction materials"],
	correctAnswer: 0},

	{question: "What is permafrost?", 
	choices: ["The thing that forms on the windshield of your car", "When you can’t reheat your leftovers", "Soil that is always at below-freezing temperatures" , "Glaciers"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What is the largest source of greenhouse gas emissions (as of 2022)?",
	choices: ["Transportation", "Power generation", "Manufacturing", "Residential"],
	correctAnswer: 0},


	{question: "Which number is commonly associated with plastics that can be recycled?",
	choices: ["1", "3", "7", "5"],
	correctAnswer: 0},

	{question: "What is the cause of the hole in the ozone layer?",
	choices: ["Methane", "Chlorofluorocarbons (CFCs)", "Volcanic activity", "Deforestation"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "What percentage of plastic waste is actually recycled globally?",
	choices: ["50%", "30%", "20%", "<10%"],
	correctAnswer: 3},

	{question: "What is an example of a climate feedback loop?",
	choices: ["Sea level rise", "People suggest polluting less", "Mass displacement from climate catastrophes", "More wildfires cause more carbon emissions"],
	correctAnswer: 3},

	{question: "What does the term biodiversity hotspot refer to?",
	choices: ["Regions with high levels of pollution", "Regions with high numbers of invasive species", "Regions with high numbers of native species", "None of the above"],
	correctAnswer: 2},


	{question: "Which of the following is not a greenhouse gas?Which number is commonly associated with plastics that can be recycled?",
	choices: ["Carbon dioxide (CO2)", "Sulfur hexafluoride (SF6)", "Hydrochloric acid (HCl)", "Methane (CH4)"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What is the primary cause of ocean acidification?",
	choices: ["Oil spills", "Plastic pollution", "Excess CO2 absorption", "Agricultural runoff"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What does upcycling mean?",
	choices: ["Turning waste into energy", "Converting waste materials into new materials of higher quality", "Reusing products without alteration", "Disposing of waste in a responsible manner"],
	correctAnswer: 1},

	{question: "Which gas is a significant contributor to the formation of acid rain?",
	choices: ["Oxygen (O2)", "Carbon dioxide (CO2)", "Sulfur dioxide (SO2)", "Nitrogen (N2)"],
	correctAnswer: 2},

	{question: "What simple action can individuals take to help prevent ozone layer depletion?",
	choices: ["Planting trees", "Using energy-efficient appliances", "Reducing the use of aerosol sprays containing CFCs", "Recycling plastic bottles"],
	correctAnswer: 2}
]
